Yiran!
Come help me peel some garlic.
What are you doing?
You've been sitting there forever.
You can't even peel garlic.
You obviously eat takeout every day.
Forget it.
Here, give it to me.
Go beat two eggs for me.
Like a bull
in a china shop.
My hand just slipped, okay?
You talk too much.
I suddenly remember when I first got married.
When I went into the kitchen, I
broke an egg too.
Your Pops said I was
like a bull
in a china shop.
Are you making chicken soup?
You've got a sharp nose.
Is it ready yet?
I'm hungry.
I'll go check.
Here.
How's the seasoning?
Not salty.
Granny Xiufang used to make chicken soup for us too.
It was so salty Chen Baixi and I almost threw up.
When people get older,
their sense of taste fades.
But even chicken soup like that,
we'll never get to have it again.
Stop acting all deep with me.
Don't cry.
From now on,
whenever you drink chicken soup,
won't you think of Granny Xiufang?
Just like me.
Whenever I go into the kitchen,
I think of your Pops.
Even though some people are gone,
as long as we, the living, remember them, that's enough.
The clothes are in the back room.
Xiwa.
Grandma found you!
Is it tasty?
It is.
Grandma, have some too.
Grandma, when I grow up,
I'll buy you lots of brown sugar glutinous rice cakes.
Okay.
My Xiwa is so sweet.
Grandma will be waiting.
Grandma doesn't know
how tall you've grown.
if she'd still recognize you.
Have you seen my boy?
My boy!
Xiwa!
Come home.
It's been twenty years.
Grandma
is taking my Xiwa home.
Xiwa!
Come home.
Before Granny passed away,
what did she say to you?
Granny...
Granny has something to tell you.
Tell me, Granny.
I know
that you
aren't my Xiwa.
But you're my good grandson.
I also know
you have something
on your mind.
Let Granny tell you this.
Look forward,
don't look back.
Don't look back.
She told me
that finding me
and having me by her side
made her very happy.
Pops.
Are you really okay with my brother doing this?
Sincerity matters more than formality.
He's the best person for it.
A stick of incense opens the path to the netherworld
Beloved parent, depart without worldly cares
May light illuminate the Three Paths
The mighty wind sweeps away impurities,
the divine light guards the path.
Grandma,
I've opened the path for you.
The silver bridge crosses worldly suffering,
the golden bridge leads to the Jade Capital.
The gentle soul steps firmly on the lotus,
To wander freely in peace forevermore.
Crossing the bridge!
Stepping on lotus flowers, rising ever higher.
The Gold Bridge leads to the highest heavens.
Granny,
You are deeply blessed.
Step firmly on the Gold Bridge and don't look back.
Crossing the bridge!
Grandma.
There's light on the bridge.
Take your time.
Cross safely.
Once you cross the bridge,
you'll see Xizi.
These sugar glutinous rice cakes,
take them with you.
Passing on won't be so bitter.
You won't have to worry about this world's
trivial matters anymore.
Please pay your respects.
First bow.
Second bow.
Third bow.
Family, return the bow.
Here.
Take this.
Here you go.
Daxi.
I'm leaving.
Stay strong.
Kid.
Look forward.
Stop spacing out.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Just saw some familiar faces.
Where?
They already left.
Boss Chen,
Eating all by yourself?
When you get old,
nobody wants you around.
I enjoy eating alone. It's quite nice.
Boss, two plates of beef slices.
Alright.
Dad.
I have something to tell you.
I know what you're gonna say.
Wait a second.
Let me speak first.
What happened with Granny Xiufang today...
Even though you broke the rules,
it was the reasonable thing to do.
The funeral industry
isn't a glamorous business.
People see it as taboo.
But it's our family's lifeblood.
What's the old saying?
It runs
in the family.
So, I want my son to carry it on,
to do our ancestors proud.
Dad...
I know.
Over this very thing,
we've been at odds for years.
I also know
you have a dream in your heart.
If you want to leave now,
I won't stop you.
After all,
people have to live for themselves.
Dad, what I actually wanted to say is...
I don't want to leave.
Not leaving?
What did you say?
Dad, what's with that look?
I said I'm not leaving, is that a problem?
You said you could only realize your dream in Beijing.
When I was in Beijing,
I took the subway every day.
Whenever I got on,
have you seen a can of sardines?
I was squeezed like a can of sardines.
Stinky and ugly.
Sometimes there wasn't even room to stand.
It was incredibly crowded.
From one audition
to another,
I even had to work odd jobs at night.
Then I had to catch the last train home.
It made me feel like
a spinning top that never stops.
Going round and round,
I didn't even know who I was anymore.
Over all these years,
the only time I gave a stellar performance
was wearing sackcloth on set for a funeral.
Crying and wailing,
like there was no tomorrow.
"Oh, Dad!"
Everyone applauded, calling me a filial son.
This is how I acted.
"Oh, Dad!
Why did you die so tragically?"
Tears just kept streaming down my face.
Are you cursing me to die, boy?
I saw it a lot with you when I was a kid.
Dad, I know
Paradise Funeral Home is your life's work,
and the root of our family.
I want to stay and help you.
Help me?
Mainly, I've felt pretty fulfilled lately.
Pretty grounded, too.
Sunrise brings hope,
sunset brings reflection.
I feel like I'm no longer drifting.
You son of a bitch.
Did you have too much to drink?
I... I haven't even started drinking yet.
Dad.
Thank you.
Kid,
our funeral business,
to put it bluntly,
comes down to two things.
The left hand
is helping the departed pass on in peace.
The right hand
is giving the living a place to cry.
In other words, this job of ours
is half in the earth,
and half
in the heart.
Once you take this step,
there's no turning back.
Of course,
if you regret it,
it's not too late.
I don't regret it.
No regrets.
Then eat up.
Eat.
The pot's boiling. Add some food.
Thanks.
In this line of work,
it's about respecting heaven, earth, others, and yourself.
Chen Baixi,
have you thought this through?
I have.
Good.
Founding Master above,
today, Chen Jianguo asks heaven, earth, and Founding Master,
if my son, Chen Baixi,
can inherit my mantle.
Ask again.
If the Founding Master truly lets him pass on the teachings,
please grant the divination blocks again.
The Founding Master
has agreed.
Kneel down.
This profession isn't just the final stop for the dead,
it's also a comfort for the living.
Remember.
Kindness first, dedication foremost.
Hold compassion in your heart, act with measure.
Comfort the hearts of the living,
rest the souls of the departed.
I will remember your teachings.
Are you sure you don't regret staying?
No regrets.
Why?
Same as you.
Maybe the evening breeze here,
more than the dreams in Beijing,
understands my worth better.
You copycat, Chen Baixi.
Oh, right.
This is for you.
For me?
You were going back to Shanghai before,
so I got a gift for you.
But then you didn't leave,
so I just
never gave it to you.
What is it?
A cheap little trinket.
It's cheap?
Then I don't want it.
No, wait.
It's cheap,
it's cheap, but it's...
it's very meaningful.
I'm opening it.
Yiran Star.
I went online and bought you
the naming rights to a star.
This is the certificate.
From now on, there's a star in the sky
that belongs to you.
Even though you can't see or touch it,
it's right there.
It'll always be there.
Thanks.
I really like it.
I'll put it away.
Where should it go?
White or black?
White.
Right.
We'll put it here.
Done.
Excellent.
Today's a good day.
You're in a good mood today.
You have no idea.
That son of a bitch of mine...
He's finally settled down.
He's decided to take over the business.
Really?
That's a huge weight off my mind.
Mom.
Uncle A Min said he'd come play today.
It's been so long, and he's not here.
A Min?
You mean our Blockhead?
Last time,
Yiran sent him to learn from me.
Then he and Yangyang became friends.
A Min...
He's just bad with people.
A Min.
I... I just got here.
Then why didn't you go in?
Okay.
Jianguo, you're here too.
Speak of the devil.
A Min, you...
Yangyang, I just wrote a new poem.
Come help me take a look.
Brother Chen.
You're getting a haircut here too?
Everyone's studying hard here, Juanzi.
Sorry.
I... I...
I forgot my money.
I'll get it right now.
I'll just pay for you.
I'd feel bad about that.
What's there to feel bad about?
We'll be family anyway.
Family?
I'm not...
You old man.
You should care about your son's marriage.
Do you get it?
You...
Okay, I get it.
Do you really get it?
I think I get it.
I get it.
Do you get it or not?
Juanzi.
That was scary.
Chen Baixi is just like his old man.
His reactions are so slow.
I seriously can't with him.
Juanzi.
I need you to do me a favor.
What is it?
I found a guy.
He's the classiest guy around here.
You two would be a perfect match.
Go on a blind date for me.
I'm not in the mood.
You're in your prime right now.
You're so beautiful.
And your career is going well.
Look, your hair is pretty.
Your ears are pretty.
Your earrings are pretty.
Your eyes are pretty.
Your eyebrows are pretty too.
Your mouth is pretty too.
Everything about you is pretty.
If you don't enjoy your youth now,
when will you?
Don't you think so?
Then it's decided.
Saturday, 5 p.m., at Magpie Bridge Tea Restaurant.
You definitely won't regret it.
It's settled.
Don't say another word.
I'm leaving.
That's that, okay?
No, wait.
Sister Lan.
Sweetie, what's up?
You haven't paid yet.
How much is it?
Just a cut is 20.
20.
Paid. See?
Got it.
Bro.
I heard Fan Shiqi gave you a present.
Baixi,
what brings you here?
While I was editing the documentary,
I also cut some clips of Granny Xiufang.
You can keep them as a memento.
Thank you.
Is there anything else?
Last time,
I said I liked you.
I just wanted to ask you again,
is there still a chance for us?
What do you think they're whispering about?
If you keep acting like this,
my brother is really gonna be stolen by Miss Fan.
What do you mean, stolen?
Your brother is a person.
He has a mind of his own.
Whoever he wants to be with
is completely up to him.
Why do I feel like the air
is thick with jealousy?
Someone's feeling sour!
Don't talk nonsense.
She just gave me some videos of Granny Xiufang.
I thought she was confessing her love to you.
Right, Yiran?
Chen Xiaofang, why are you such a gossip?
If you have time to mind other people's business,
you'd better mind your own first.
Not him again.
Bro, hurry up and kick him out.
I don't want to see him.
I heard from Wu Huilian
that Zhou Fang is left with nothing now.
His dad supposedly took back his car and house.
He's completely penniless now,
fending for himself.
He even texted me yesterday to borrow money.
Xiaofang, aren't you gonna do anything?
Who knows if he's pretending to be pitiful to trick me?
Just hear what he has to say first.
Go on, go on.
Zhou Fang.
I heard you got kicked out of the house.
Xiaofang.
I chose to leave.
Young Master Zhou,
are you really willing to give up the silver spoon?
For you,
I'm willing to give up anything.
Save the high-sounding nonsense.
Chen Xiaofang.
I, Zhou Fang, swear.
Even without my family's help,
I can make something of myself.
What's he saying?
He made a vow,
and then he raised his hand.
Don't just be passionate for a couple of days
and then go back to being daddy's little boy.
I admit I was a jerk before,
but I'm serious now.
I'm not a very patient person.
I can't wait too long.
I won't make you wait too long.
I'm going back to work hard right now.
Oh my god!
Young Boss Zhou.
Are you trying to murder me?
You scared me to death.
I just got a bit excited seeing you.
I just sold my sports car,
and just learned how to ride a bike.
Thought I'd use it to get some exercise.
Oh, really?
This bike is pretty nice.
The seat's not very comfortable.
How's yours?
Making yourself at home.
If I'd known being shameless was this useful,
I would've ditched my pride long ago.
What's the point of saving face anyway?
If saving face were actually useful,
a lot of things would never get done.
I'm just keeping Auntie Huilan's words
firmly in mind.
How did it go again?
She said, the thickness of your wallet determines the height of your love.
It's just that...
I've almost spent all the money from my sports car.
No worries.
Yiran said it herself.
When doing things,
you need to focus.
Addition is human nature,
subtraction is wisdom.
I think our Joy Bells
really needs a major reform.
Auntie Huilan, what brilliant idea do you have now?
Let's go.
Let's go back and hold a reform meeting.
I'll tell you all about it.
Our slogan is,
Joyful and harmonious,
marry with Xidongdong.
Sit down.
Old Wu, you're up.
Boss, have a seat.
I'll begin now.
I made this presentation.
It's called Spicy Love.
We've all had hot pot, right?
You know it's divided into spicy and clear broth.
Why is it divided like that?
Because everyone's taste is different.
Well, people are the same way.
Divided into I-person (introvert) and E-person (extrovert).
So, we
need to separate these two types of people into different groups.
Let's talk about the I-person (introvert) first.
An I-person (introvert) needs to wear a mask
for soul-level socializing.
They can't see your face,
but they can read your heart.
We've all seen plenty of I-persons.
They don't speak or make a sound.
So our Joy Bells
just needs to create a good social environment for them.
Do you think it's the eighties?
It's so tacky.
Wumei.
You son of a bitch, you workplace slacker.
All talk and no action.
Who's older?
Even though I'm older than you,
my heart is still young.
If you don't want to be an old slacker,
then get your ass out of the frying pan!
Work with me. Do you dare?
Fine, I will.
You think I'm scared of you?
What are you doing?
Looking all down in the dumps.
Your fingernails look pretty nice today.
Press-on nails. You wouldn't get it, bumpkin.
Here, they're yours.
For me?
This set is too small for me to wear anyway.
This event of ours,
if it fails, the company will go bankrupt.
Then I'll just have to go to Chengdu to work.
If you go to Chengdu,
Young Boss Zhou will definitely miss you.
I know you all might be a little nervous.
But don't worry.
Here,
you can take off your usual social masks,
and connect with each other sincerely.
Let's get started.
Then tonight,
can I invite you to dinner?
Sure.
Is that okay?
I gotta say,
this actually works pretty well.
Right?
Let's take a picture together.
Sure!
I'll take it.
I feel like I've known you forever.
We're going to be together forever.
E-person Special
The E-person Special is a hunting ground for love.
Reveal your true feelings amidst adventure and thrills.
You've all seen an E-person, right?
They just love to chat.
And love to socialize.
We just need to provide them
with a special environment,
boost their enthusiasm and sense of responsibility,
get them excited,
and the little sparks of love will ignite.
Hey.
Escape Room.
Murder mystery game.
None of the above!
My dear E-person friends,
this is your hunting ground for love.
Here, you'll find not only the challenge of solving puzzles,
but also the thrill of hearts connecting.
Are you sure what's burning is a spark of love?
Don't let it turn out to be just flying sparks.
It wouldn't be good if they fly everywhere and burn someone.
What is love, anyway?
If you're scared of every little thing,
then that's not love.
Love is just like instant noodles.
Too fast, and they're undercooked.
Too slow, and they turn to mush.
They have to soak for just the right amount of time.
When they burn your mouth just a little bit,
that's when they're perfect.
Simply put,
young love is a burning passion.
Let it burn when it should!
Thanks, boss!
Success!
I... These shoes are made in Italy.
That stomp just cost you half a year's salary.
You hear me?
I'm really sorry.
I didn't see you.
I'm sorry.
Are you brain-dead?
So clumsy.
Home Funeral Paradise
What a crappy name.
Seriously,
you don't even have a waiter here?
Sir.
This isn't a restaurant.
Why would we have waiters?
Sorry about that.
Xiaofang.
I'm so sorry.
What kind of services are you looking for, sir?
Little punk, are you a waiter?